Guide to the Cedric N. Chatterley Photographs, 1983-2008 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- MFA Thesis Series, 1987, (2 boxes)
  - 18x24 Prints:
    - MFA thesis #15 bottom (below #14, top)
    - MFA thesis #16 top (above #17, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #17 bottom (below #16, top)
    - MFA thesis #18 top (above #19, bottom) with open Bible
    - MFA thesis #19 bottom (below #18, top)
    - MFA thesis #20 top (above #21, bottom) Bible/pulpit (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #21 bottom (below #20, top)
    - MFA thesis #22 top (above #23, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #23 bottom (below #22, top)
    - MFA thesis #24 top (above #25, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #25 bottom (below #24, top)
    - MFA thesis #26 top (above #27, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #27 bottom (below #26, top)
    - MFA thesis #28 top (above #29, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #29 bottom (below #28, top)
    - MFA thesis #30 top (above #31, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #31 bottom (below #30, top)
    - MFA thesis #32 top (above #33, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #33 bottom (below #32, top)
    - MFA thesis #34 top (above #35, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #35 bottom (below #34, top)
    - MFA thesis #36 top (above #37, bottom)
    - MFA thesis #37 bottom (below #36, top)
    - MFA thesis #38
    - MFA thesis #39
    - MFA thesis #40
- Penobscot Poultry Series, 1988-1994, (6 boxes)
  Consists of 91 11x14 and ten 16x20 gelatin silver prints. On February 24, 1988, Penobscot Poultry in Belfast, Maine closed down. Chatterley documented the final days of the last chicken processing plant in the state and followed former employee Linda Lord as she sought new employment afterwards. The plant became the subject of the book, I Was Content and Not Content: The Story of Linda Lord and the Closing of Penobscot Poultry by Alicia J. Rouverol and Stephen A. Cole, with Chatterley contributing the photographs. Original captions, with Chatterley's contextual side comments, taken from back of prints. Arranged chronologically.
  - Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" (I did not know she was there when I made this photograph during the first tour in mid-February, 1988). Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Workers taking a break inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, (final day) 1988 Feb. 24
  - Two workers in the break room not far from the "blood tunnel" on Penobscot Poultry's final day, 1988 Feb. 24. Belfast, Maine.
  - Linda Lord and co-workers in the break room nearest the "blood tunnel" on Penobscot Poultry's closing day, Feb. 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine. (This was before I saw Linda at work inside the blood tunnel. I had not spoken to her yet or introduced myself.)
  - Workers turning in their smocks on the final day of Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. 24
  - Line worker and foreman embrace on the final day of Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. 24
  - Poultry barn near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Poultry barn near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Hatchery in Waldo County, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Worker at Bayside Industries Hatchery, Unity, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Husband and wife team "sexing" young chicks at Bayside Industries Hatchery near Unity, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Clean-up time, first visit to Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Trucks with live chickens entering Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Trucks with empty crates exiting Penobscot Poultry's loading dock-from the second story window. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Workers ("hangers") outside on the loading dock at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Workers ("hangers") outside on the loading dock at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Workers ("hangers") outside on the loading dock at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Dead chickens, expired before exiting their crates, loading dock at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Workers, boxes, ice, scale, roller conveyor inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Poultry, after being hung, move toward Penobscot Poultry's interior. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Workers transferring poultry from conveyor to another. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Poultry after being run through the scalder and about to go into the de-feathering machine in Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Poultry exiting the de-feathering machine in Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Poultry coming out of the de-feathering machine. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Coming and going from the de-feathering machine. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - One of several open flames to singe pinfeathers/hair. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Poultry shackled on a moving conveyor, passing a gas flame to remove hair, pinfeathers. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Poultry passing over gas-lit flame to remove pin-hairs/feathers. Inspector stands and inspects. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Inspector cutting away bruised parts. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Inspector cutting away bruised parts. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Inspectors at a conveyor belt inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Inspector standing near window inside Penobscot Poultry-overlooking Penobscot Bay. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Workers on "Line One" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - The "neck puller." Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Necks in a holding tank. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - The eviscerating line. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - The eviscerating line. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Worker reaching in to pull intestines on the eviscerating line inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Workers on the "cut up line" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Upstairs in "Further processing" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Upstairs in "Further processing" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Workers upstairs in "Further processing." Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Workers upstairs in "Further processing." Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Worker at machine that manages chicken hearts (and possibly gizzards) inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Rendering room, Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Stacking ready to ship packages of chicken to be shipped. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Automatic neck-cutting device in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Workers at the Cry-o-vac (bagging) machine. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Man with bagged sandwich watches a friend at the box machine. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Freezer lockers, Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Break area, Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Workers taking a break. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Worker looking for pocket change to put in the vending machine at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Hallway near lunchroom. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Announcement board inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Hosing down - clean up time at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb.
  - Penobscot Poultry, center of image. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Penobscot Poultry a few weeks after it closed. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Linda Lord hanging clothes on her front porch. There is a plastic barrier to keep out winter winds. 1988, Mar.
  - Linda Lord helping her friend, Roxie, catch and slaughter a half-dozen chickens. Near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Linda Lord in Roxie's yard-catching and slaughtering chickens. Near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Linda Lord and her friend, Roxie, cutting up chickens. Near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Linda Lord backing a truck into the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. building. Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Linda Lord backing a truck into the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. garage. Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Linda Lord (on top of truck) during routine fire drill. Brooks City Park, Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Linda Lord at a resume writing workshop inside the Belfast Curling Club, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Mar.
  - Two photographs of Linda Lord. On the back of one, her father, Philip, wrote: My sleepy time girl and her first deer. (The photographs are on Linda's kitchen table.) Brooks, Maine, 1988 Apr. (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord and others taking a test for Champion Paper Co. at the Coastal Economic Development Office. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Apr.
  - Linda Lord serving food at the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. Benefit Supper. Brooks, Maine, 1988 Apr.
  - Linda Lord at the Brooks Volunteer Fire Department Supper. Brooks, Maine, 1988 Apr.
  - Entering Brooks, Maine (from the south) on Rt. 7. 1988 Apr.
  - Chickens entering Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 June
  - Linda Lord crossing her front yard. (The house once belonged to her grandmother). Brooks, Maine, 1988 June
  - Linda Lord learning computer skills at the Coastal Economic Development Office. Belfast, Maine, 1988 June
  - Linda Lord checking the job announcement board at the Coastal Economic Development Office. Belfast, Maine, 1988 June
  - Linda Lord playing drums with the Golden Nuggets at a campground in Dixmont, Maine, 1988 June
  - Linda Lord playing drums with the Golden Nuggets at a campground in Dixmont, Maine, 1988 June
  - Linda Lord in the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. truck on her way to participate in a 4th of July parade in Unity, Maine, 1988.
  - Untitled print depicting Linda Lord affixing American flags to the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. truck on the July 4, 1988.
  - Belfast, Maine from Rt. 1. 1988 Summer.
  - Linda Lord looking into a rope-making machine inside Belfast Rope. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Sept.
  - Linda Lord untangling small material inside Belfast Rope during her first week. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Sept.
  - Phillip Lord (Linda's father), Linda, and Bandit in the garden behind their house in Brooks, Maine, 1992 Summer
  - Bandit giving Linda Lord a kiss in front of her home (where she was born) in Brooks, Maine, 1994 Summer
  - Linda Lord on her three-wheeled motorcycle in downtown Brooks, Maine, 1994 Summer
  - Downtown Belfast, Maine, 1994 Summer
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" on Penobscot Poultry's final day of production, February 24, 1988. (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry on its final day of production, February 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine.
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry on its final day of production, February 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine.
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry on its last day of production, February 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine.
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry on its final day of production, February 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine.
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord applying for unemployment benefits for the first time in her life. The American Legion Hall, Post 43, Belfast, Maine. 1988 Mar. 1
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord showing her high school senior portrait. Rollie's Cafe, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Mar. 15
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in Belfast Rope. 1988 Sept. 12
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work. Belfast Rope, 1988 Sept.
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work inside Belfast Rope. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Sept.
- David "Honeyboy" Edwards Series, 1990-1996 and undated, (4 boxes)
  Consists of 107 11x14 selenium-toned gelatin silver prints documenting Mississippi Delta blues guitarist David "Honeyboy" Edwards. Images were taken between 1990 and 1996 and typically feature Honeyboy and the places he visited while touring the southern and midwestern United States. In some shots, fellow blues musicians appear with Honeyboy in concerts and recording sessions. Original captions with Chatterley's contextual side comments were taken from back of prints. Arranged chronologically.
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards just outside the back door at Rosa's Lounge on the 4th of July weekend, 1990, Chicago, Illinois (This was my first photo session with Honeyboy) (Box 15)
  - (Contact negative) David "Honeyboy" Edwards with newly made friend, Chicago Blues Festival, 1991 June
  - Dvaid "Honeyboy" Edwards in the recording studio on New Year's Eve, 1991. Recording "Delta Bluesman" for Earwig Records. Chicago, Illinois
  - Sunnyland Slim (Albert Luandrew) in the recording studio for Honeyboy's "Delta Bluesman.' New Year's Eve, 1991
  - Sunnyland Slim (Albert Luandrew) in the recording studio helping Honeyboy record "Delta Bluesman." Chicago, Illinois, New Year's Eve, 1991
  - Carey Bell blowing harp for Honeyboy's "Delta Bluesman" recording in Chicago, Illinois, New Year's Eve, 1991
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards outside recording studio, Belmont Street, Chicago, Illinois (after recording for "Delta Bluesman." New Year's Eve, 1991
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards performing at the first Robert Johnson Memorial Blues Festival in Greenwood, Mississippi, June 1992. Perhaps the most spirited performance I ever saw him give.
  - (Two negatives printed consecutively) David "Honeyboy" Edwards and John Hammond, Jr. at the 1st Annual Robert Johnson Blues Festival, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 June
  - Hallway bathroom in the Riverside Hotel, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992 June
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards in the Riverside Hotel, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992 June
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards showing dice tricks he learned from Big Joe Williams. The Riverside Hotel, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992 June
  - The David Lyndsay Band performing on a June Sunday morning near Maxwell Street, Chicago, Illinois, 1992.
  - Lonnie Pitchford and David "Honeyboy" Edwards backstage at the Chicago Blues Festival, 1992 June
  - Rosedale, Mississippi, 1992 June
  - Passing Parchman's Farm-Mississippi State Penitentiary, south of Tutwiler, 1992 July
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards inside a small grocery store in Shaw, Mississippi-his hometown, 1992 July
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards talking with some local folks on Johnson Street, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 July
  - (Contact negatives) David "Honeyboy" Edwards, live at Blind Willie's in Atlanta, Georgia, 1992 Aug.
  - Issaquena Street, downtown Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992, Summer
  - Small grocer on Issaquena St., downtown Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992 Summer
  - (Two 35mm negatives printed consecutively) David "Honeyboy" Edwards purchasing a new wallet in a drug store in downtown Clarksdale, Mississippi. Two blocks away in the Delta Blues Museum at the Muddy Waters display, 1992 Summer
  - (Contact negatives) Left: Honeyboy visiting an old friend behind his cousin's repair shop, Shaw, Mississippi. Right: Honeyboy searching for his mother's unmarked gravesite, just outside Shaw, 1992 Summer
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards and another man sharing stories of people they both knew many years prior. Chris' Cafe, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 Summer
  - Men folding the state flag, Leflore County Courthouse, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 Summer
  - Storage building for Shellmound Plantation, outside Greenwood, Mississippi. This was once a county store and Honeyboy met Sonny Boy Williamson (Rice Miller) at this location. Honeyboy was 14 years old at the time, 1992 Summer
  - Bridge over the Tallahatchie River, outside Greenwood, Mississippi. Honeyboy walked this bridge countless times as a youth, 1992 Summer
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards signing a copy of White Windows for Sonny Payne, Director of the radio station's King Biscuit Blues Hour in Helena, Arkansas. (Michael Frank, left), 1992 Summer
  - West Helena, Arkansas. For Honeyboy's "West Helena Blues" - the song with which he begins nearly every live performance, 1992 Summer (Box 16)
  - Eddie's Tavern, Helena, Arkansas, 1992 Summer
  - Helena, Arkansas, 1992 Summer
  - S. Rampart Street, New Orleans, Louisiana. Honeyboy said he lived on this block for a short time, 1992 Summer
  - New Orleans, Louisiana - from the I90 Bridge (Gentilly Blvd) looking toward the Interstate 10 Bridge, 1992 Sept.
  - The location where Honeyboy Edwards met Robert Johnson (the lot just behind this young man) on Johnson Street, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 Sept.
  - Seven contacts of the acreage where David "Honeyboy" Edwards birthplace home once stood 1 mile outside Shaw. The final two contacts are downtown Shaw, Mississippi, 1992 Sept.
  - Contact negative of abandoned house in Lula, north of Clarksdale, Mississippi, where Honeyboy lived for a short period of time in the 1940s, 1992 Oct.
  - Abandoned bar near the Mississippi/Alabama border (east of Philadelphia, MS), 1992 Fall
  - Men burning the plastic off copper wire to salvage the contents for cash. Chicago's south side, 1992
  - Wildwood Plantation near Money, Mississippi, where Honeyboy lived as a child. - The building, which was once a store, on Shellmound Plantation near Greenwood, Mississippi, where Honeyboy met Sonny Boy Williamson (Rice Miller). - The boyhood Missionary Baptist Church (Sweet Home M.B.C.) near Money, Mississippi. All 1992, (3 contact prints)
  - Man standing in downtown Tutwiler, Mississippi, across from where the train depot had been, and where W.C. Handy had his famous encounter with an old man playing the blues (when Handy woke from a nap) - Abandoned church near the burial place of Sonny Boy Williamson (Rice Miller) - Downtown Tutwiler again (same street, looking toward the train depot spot), 1992, (3 contact prints)
  - From the Martin Luther King Bridge (crosses the Mississippi River), East St. Louis, Illinois. One of my two favorite landscape images in the entire body of work, 1993 Mar.
  - Kentucky side of the Ohio/Mississippi River confluence - just south of Cairo, Illinois. High water, 1993 Mar.
  - Honeyboy preparing for evening concert (we were snowed in). Scottish Inn, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1993 Mar.
  - Tuning up prior to performance. Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1993 Mar.
  - Fish store, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1993 Mar.
  - Vicksburg, Mississippi, 1993 Mar.
  - Civil War monument, Vicksburg, Mississippi, 1993 Mar.
  - Bridge connecting Mississippi and Louisiana. Vicksburg, Miss, 1993 Mar.
  - Downtown Shaw, Mississippi, hometown of David Honeyboy Edwards, 1993 Mar.
  - Bridge over Tallahatchie River, near Ft. Loring (south of Greenwood), Mississippi, 1993 Mar.
  - Beginning of a snow/sleet storm in Greenwood, Mississippi, 1993 Mar.
  - Cemetery where Charlie Patton is buried, just outside Holly Ridge, Mississippi. Snow/sleet in March, 1993.
  - Elijah Newsome inside his World of Music (Blues shack). Itta Bena, Mississippi, 1993 Mar.
  - Contact sheet of Elijah Newsome's Blues shack, Itta Bena, Mississippi, 1993 Mar.
  - Bay St. Louis, Mississippi - near the location where Honeyboy and Big Joe Williams parted ways in the 1930s. One of my two favorite landscape images in the entire body of work, 1993 Mar.
  - Fire, Erath, Louisiana, 1993 Mar. (Box 17)
  - New Orleans, Louisiana, 1993 Mar. (Street scene of telephone pole with "Thou Shalt Not Kill" sign.)
  - S. Rampart Street (the apartments where Honeyboy lived for a short time are now gone - they were just the other side of the two-story building). New Orleans, Louisiana, 1993 Mar.
  - Holding room in Avoyelles Parish Courthouse, Marksville, Louisiana (birthplace of Honeyboy's good friend "Little Walter" or Marion Jacobs, 1993 Mar.
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards after performing at the Chicago Blues Festival, June 1993
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards at his 78th birthday party - Rosa's Lounge, Chicago, Illinois - 4th of July weekend, 1993.
  - Stairwell, Aberdeen, Mississippi, 1993 Oct.
  - Sweet Home Missionary Baptist Church (Honeyboy's childhood church) near Money, Mississippi, 1993 Oct.
  - Closed department store, downtown Helena, Arkansas, 1993 Oct.
  - Alley outside the Hole in the Wall bar in downtown Helena, Arkansas. This is where Honeyboy and his future wife, Bessie, had their first conversation. 1993 Oct.
  - Watching Honeyboy from inside his front room window on S. Wells Street. (Honeyboy's Lincoln is in the frame.) Near 43rd, Southside Chicago, 1994 Winter
  - Alice Edwards, Honeyboy's sister-in-law, holding the only existing photograph of Honeyboy's mother, Pearl Edwards. Chicago, Illinois, 1994 Winter
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards (seated) surrounded by his extended family (at his sister-in-law's house - Alice Edwards). Chicago, Illinois, 1994 Winter
  - Parting ways after the family portrait session, in front of Honeyboy's sister-in-law's place (Alice Edwards). Honeyboy's son, David, is waving. He would pass away two years later. Chicago, Illinois, 1994 Winter
  - Man walking, Southside Chicago (47th Street), 1994 Winter
  - Wig store, Southside Chicago (Halstead Street), 1994 Winter
  - Parking lot for fish store on Chicago's Southside. The truck comes up from Mississippi and other states with live fish, 1994 Winter
  - Mississippi River, Memphis, Tennessee, 1994 Winter
  - Just south of Houston's downtown (5th ward), Texas, 1994 Spring
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards holding a t-shirt - to be signed for a fan - for Albert "Sunnyland Slim" Luandrew at the the Chicago Blues Festival, 1994 June
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards at Chicago Blues Festival, 1994 June
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards cousin, Willie Mae Powell, for whom Robert Johnson wrote "Love in Vain." She and Robert Johnson dated off and on before his death. Her front yard, outside Tunica, Mississippi, 1994 Oct.
  - Honeyboy's cousin, Willie Mae Powell, laughing in her front yard. She dated Robert Johnson for a period of time. Outside Tunica, Mississippi, 1994 Oct.
  - Child's tomb next to Sweet Home Missionary Baptist Church near Money, Mississippi, 1994 Oct.
  - Cotton harvest near Money, Mississippi, 1994 Oct.
  - Cotton harvest near Money, Mississippi, 1994 Oct.
  - Just outside the long-closed Hole in the Wall bar, downtown Helena, Arkansas, 1994 Oct. (Box 18)
  - Honeyboy at the King Biscuit Blues Festival. Helena, Arkansas, 1994 Oct.
  - Big Bad Smitty (John H. Smith) playing guitar in Eddie's Tavern, downtown Helena, Arkansas, about an hour following the closing of the King Biscuit Blues Festival, 1994 Oct.
  - Looking through glass of cafe on Oretha Castle Haley Blvd., New Orleans, Louisiana, 1994 Oct.
  - Abandoned church, Memphis, Tennessee, 1994
  - Near Barlow, Kentucky, heading towards Cairo, Illinois, 1995 Winter
  - Heading north on Highway 51 - leaving Mounds, Illinois, 1995 Winter
  - Apparatus used to engrave stone gravesite memorials. Bell Monuments, Cairo, Illinois, 1995 Winter
  - Abandoned meat packing plant, Southside Chicago, 1995 Winter
  - Amtrak passing through Chicago's Southside, heading north, 1995 Winter
  - Friends jamming. South 47th Street storefront, Chicago, Illinois, 1995 Winter
  - Man selling cassette tapes, South 47th Street, Chicago, Illinois, 1995 Winter
  - (Image of Jesus) Southside Chicago, 1995 Winter
  - Honeyboy's young friend, Charles, whom he often watched after, sitting in the kitchen with a guitar Honeyboy had given him. On Wells Street, near 43rd, Southside Chicago, 1995 Winter
  - Man mowing, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1995 Spring